Contact

Ciudad de México, CDMX 525554729259 (Mobile) victorgallo.financiero@gmai l.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ victorgallofinanciero (LinkedIn) techflow.agency (Personal)

Top Skills

Design Thinking
Web Applications
Data Science

Languages

Español

Inglés (Full Professional)

Certifications

Introduction to cyber security

Asesor en estrategias de inversion figura 3

CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript

CS50 Introduction to programming with Python

Honors-Awards
CFA Exam

Victor Gallo

Intelligent Creative. Front-End Developer | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | React | API`S | GIT |

Mexico City, Mexico

Summary

Intelligent Creative. Front-End Developer | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | React | API`S | GIT |

Technical knowledge, practical experience, analytical, business background, competitive, user-friendly, good problem-solving and idea generation, curiosity, risk assumption, self-management, openness, focus, good communication, charisma, game-changer.

Experience

Techflow.agency
Web Developer
June 2021 - Present (2 years)
Mexico City, Mexico

Enthusiastic web developer passionate about technology, innovation, and marketing strategies to scale businesses.

Globant

Account Executive December 2022 - May 2023 (6 months) Ciudad de México, México

ASTER Expansión

Sales Manager January 2021 - July 2022 (1 year 7 months)

Team management.

Customer service.

Sales

BanBajío

Account Executive

August 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 1 month)

León, Guanajuato, México

Financial Advisor
Sales of financial products
Customer service

Education

Escuela Bancaria y Comercial

Bachelor's degree, Accounting and Finance · (August 2015 - August 2019)